Guide to the Harvey Williams Cushing Papers in the Yale University Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers held in Manuscripts and Archives, Part I
  - Special Files, 1886-1939; Series II; 43.75 linear feet (98 boxes, 49 reels)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: general, 1903, 1910-1916 (Box 141, Folder 631, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A-C, 1920-1923 (Box 141, Folder 632, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: E-M, 1920-1923 (Box 141, Folder 633, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: N-S, 1920-1923 (Box 141, Folder 634, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: T-X, 1920-1923 (Box 142, Folder 635, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A-C, 1924-1926 (Box 142, Folder 636, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: D-E, 1924-1926 (Box 142, Folder 637, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: G, 1925-1926 (Box 142, Folder 638, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: H-W, 1924-1926 (Box 142, Folder 639, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A, 1927-1928 (Box 142, Folder 640, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: B-G, 1927-1928 (Box 142, Folder 641, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: L-M, 1927-1928 (Box 142, Folder 642, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: O-V, 1927-1928 (Box 142, Folder 643, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A-B, 1929-1930 (Box 142, Folder 644, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: C, 1929-1930 (Box 142, Folder 645, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: E-H, 1929-1930 (Box 142, Folder 646, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: I-W, 1929-1930 (Box 142, Folder 647, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A-B, 1931-1933 (Box 142, Folder 648, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: C-L, 1931-1933 (Box 142, Folder 649, Reel 85)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: M-W, 1931-1933 (Box 142, Folder 650, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: A-L, 1934-1939 (Box 142, Folder 651, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of Dr. Cushing: M-W, 1934-1939 (Box 143, Folder 652, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: A-B, 1921-1931 (Box 143, Folder 653, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: C-D, 1922-1932 (Box 143, Folder 654, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: E-F, 1923-1932 (Box 143, Folder 655, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: G-L, 1921-1939 (Box 143, Folder 656, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: M-N, 1922-1934 (Box 143, Folder 657, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: O-S, 1922-1933 (Box 143, Folder 658, Reel 86)
    - Medical publications of staff: T-W, 1922-1936 (Box 143, Folder 659, Reel 86)
    - Medical Society of London address, 1927 (Box 143, Folder 660, Reel 86)
    - Meningiomas: bibliography, undated (Box 144, Reel 86)
    - Meningiomas: book reviews, 1938-1939 (Box 145, Folder 661, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas: congratulatory correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 145, Folder 662, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: A-B, 1930-1937 (Box 145, Folder 663, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: C, 1924-1937 (Box 145, Folder 664, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: D-F, 1928-1937 (Box 145, Folder 665, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: G, 1932-1937 (Box 145, Folder 666, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: H, 1927-1938 (Box 145, Folder 667, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: I-K, 1932-1937 (Box 145, Folder 668, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: L-M, 1932-1938 (Box 145, Folder 669, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: N-P, 1933-1938 (Box 145, Folder 670, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: R-S, 1921-1938 (Box 145, Folder 671, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: T, 1929-1937 (Box 145, Folder 672, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: V-W, 1933-1938 (Box 145, Folder 673, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Freese, Ruth, 1925-1937 (Box 146, Folder 674, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: George Banta Publishing Company, 1937 July-November (Box 146, Folder 675, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: George Banta Publishing Company, 1937 December (Box 146, Folder 676, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: George Banta Publishing Company, 1938 January-May (Box 146, Folder 677, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: George Banta Publishing Company, 1938 June-September (Box 146, Folder 678, Reel 87)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1933, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 679, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1938 January-March (Box 146, Folder 680, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1938 April (Box 146, Folder 681, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1938 May-July (Box 146, Folder 682, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1938 August-December (Box 146, Folder 683, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Correspondence: Thomas, Charles C., 1939 (Box 146, Folder 684, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: errors, 1938 (Box 146, Folder 685, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: miscellanea, 1939 (Box 146, Folder 686, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: notes, undated (Box 146, Folder 687, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: notes, undated (Box 146, Folder 688, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: notes, undated (Box 146, Folder 689, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Patient notebook: A-C, undated (Box 146, Folder 690, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Patient notebook: D-H, undated (Box 147, Folder 691, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Patient notebook: I-O, undated (Box 147, Folder 692, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Patient notebook: P-Z, undated (Box 147, Folder 693, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas Patient notebook: Louise Eisenhardt's little black book, undated (Box 147, Folder 694, Reel 88)
    - Meningiomas: patient notes, undated (Box 147, Folder 695, Reel 89)
    - Meningiomas: statistics, undated (Box 147, Folder 696, Reel 89)
    - Mickle Fellowship, 1922 (Box 147, Folder 697, Reel 89)
    - Mumford, James Gregory, 1910-1915 (Box 147, Folder 698, Reel 89)
      See also: Series III, Folder 315
    - National institute for neurology
      See: Series I, Folders 1038-1039
    - New Haven, 1932-1933 (Box 147, Folder 699, Reel 89)
    - New Haven, 1934 (Box 147, Folder 700, Reel 89)
    - New Haven, 1935-1936 (Box 148, Folder 701, Reel 89)
    - New Haven, 1937-1939 (Box 148, Folder 702, Reel 89)
    - New York World's Fair, 1938-1939 (Box 148, Folder 703, Reel 89)
    - Nobel Prize, 1928-1939 (Box 148, Folder 704, Reel 89)
    - Osler, Lady Grace, 1919-1936 (Box 148, Folder 705, Reel 89)
    - Osler, Sir William, 1894-1937 (Box 148, Folder 706, Reel 89)
    - Osler, Sir William, 1897-1919 (Box 148, Folder 707, Reel 89)
    - Osler, Sir William, undated (Box 148, Folder 708, Reel 89)
    - Osler anniversary volume, 1918-1921 (Box 148, Folder 709, Reel 89)
    - Osler Club, 1928-1935 (Box 148, Folder 710, Reel 89)
    - Paré's Oeuvres, 1928 (Box 149, Folder 711, Reel 89)
    - Parker, Peter, 1916, 1934-1935 (Box 149, Folder 712, Reel 89)
    - Passports, 1920-1938 (Box 149, Folder 713, Reel 90)
    - Pasteur centenary, 1922-1923 (Box 149, Folder 714, Reel 90)
    - Patient accounts, 1915-1922 (Box 150, Reel 90)
    - Patient accounts, 1923-1926 (Box 151, Reel 91)
    - Patient accounts, 1927-1931 (Box 152, Reel 92)
    - Patient accounts: consultations notebook, 1919-1939 (Box 153, Folder 715, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: A-B, 1927-1932 (Box 153, Folder 716, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: C, 1927-1931 (Box 153, Folder 717, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: D-F, 1924-1931 (Box 153, Folder 718, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: G, 1927-1931 (Box 153, Folder 719, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: H, 1926-1931 (Box 153, Folder 720, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: I-K, 1926-1931 (Box 153, Folder 721, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: L, 1926-1932 (Box 153, Folder 722, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: Langley, Lora V., 1927-1932 (Box 153, Folder 723, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: M-O, 1926-1932 (Box 153, Folder 724, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: P-Pm, 1926-1931 (Box 153, Folder 725, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: Pn-Pz, 1926-1931 (Box 153, Folder 726, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: R, 1925-1932 (Box 154, Folder 727, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: S, 1926-1932 (Box 154, Folder 728, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: T-V, 1926-1932 (Box 154, Folder 729, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: W-Z, 1926-1932 (Box 154, Folder 730, Reel 93)
    - Patient accounts: early office records, 1905-1906, undated (Box 154, Folder 731, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1910-1912 (Box 154, Folder 732, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 154, Folder 733, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1916-1921 (Box 154, Folder 734, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 154, Folder 735, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1925 (Box 154, Folder 736, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1926 (Box 154, Folder 737, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1927 (Box 154, Folder 738, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1928 (Box 154, Folder 739, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1929 (Box 154, Folder 740, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1930 (Box 155, Folder 741, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1931 (Box 155, Folder 742, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: general correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 155, Folder 743, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: assistant residency, 1926-1931 (Box 155, Folder 744, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Employment bureau: A-M, 1920-1933 (Box 155, Folder 745, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Employment bureau: N-Z, 1916-1931 (Box 155, Folder 746, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital House officer applications: A-D, 1915-1932 (Box 155, Folder 747, Reel 94)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital House officer applications: F-G, 1915-1932 (Box 155, Folder 748, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital House officer applications: H-P, 1915-1932 (Box 155, Folder 749, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital House officer applications: R-Z, 1915-1932 (Box 155, Folder 750, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: house officer examinations, 1914-1932 (Box 155, Folder 751, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: house officer programs, 1926-1929 (Box 155, Folder 752, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Husted, Mary S., 1913-1915 (Box 155, Folder 753, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Neurological assistants: A-Da, 1915-1932 (Box 156, Folder 754, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Neurological assistants: Do-G, 1915-1932 (Box 156, Folder 755, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Neurological assistants: H-O, 1915-1932 (Box 156, Folder 756, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Neurological assistants: P-Z, 1915-1932 (Box 156, Folder 757, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Nurses Training School, 1920-1935 (Box 156, Folder 758, Reel 95)
      See also: Folder 792
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: office supplies, 1920-1927 (Box 156, Folder 759, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: office supplies, 1928-1933 (Box 156, Folder 760, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Out-patient Department, 1915-1929 (Box 156, Folder 761, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Peters (George Gorham) Travelling Fellowship, 1929-1930 (Box 156, Folder 762, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Peters (George Gorham) Travelling Fellowship, 1931-1937 (Box 156, Folder 763, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: positions available elsewhere, 1927-1932 (Box 156, Folder 764, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Recommendations to other places: A-D, 1916-1936 (Box 156, Folder 765, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Recommendations to other places: F-J, 1916-1936 (Box 156, Folder 766, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Recommendations to other places: K-Ma, 1915-1936 (Box 156, Folder 767, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Recommendations to other places: Me-N, 1915-1934 (Box 156, Folder 768, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Recommendations to other places: O-P, 1916-1935 (Box 157, Folder 769, Reel 95)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Recommendations to other places: R-Z, 1916-1935 (Box 157, Folder 770, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: reunion, tenth, 1923 (Box 157, Folder 771, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: reunion, fifteenth, 1928 (Box 157, Folder 772, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: reunion, twenty-fifth, 1938 March-April 7 (Box 157, Folder 773, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: reunion, twenty-fifth, 1938 April 12-June (Box 157, Folder 774, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Shattuck (F. C.) Fund, 1915-1931 (Box 157, Folder 775, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Social Service Department, 1915-1932 (Box 157, Folder 776, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff meetings, 1921-1926 (Box 157, Folder 777, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1910-1911 (Box 157, Folder 778, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1912-1913 (Box 157, Folder 779, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1914-1916 (Box 157, Folder 780, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1917 (Box 157, Folder 781, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1919-1920 (Box 157, Folder 782, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1921-1923 (Box 157, Folder 783, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1924 (Box 157, Folder 784, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1925-1926 (Box 158, Folder 785, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1927 (Box 158, Folder 786, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1928 (Box 158, Folder 787, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1929 (Box 158, Folder 788, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1930 (Box 158, Folder 789, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1931 (Box 158, Folder 790, Reel 96)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: staff/trustees, 1932-1936 (Box 158, Folder 791, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent of nurses, 1917-1932 (Box 158, Folder 792, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1910-1912 (Box 158, Folder 793, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1914-1915 (Box 158, Folder 794, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1916 (Box 158, Folder 795, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1917 (Box 158, Folder 796, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1919-1920 (Box 158, Folder 797, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 798, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1923 (Box 159, Folder 799, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1924 (Box 159, Folder 800, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1925 (Box 159, Folder 801, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1926 (Box 159, Folder 802, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1927 (Box 159, Folder 803, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1928 (Box 159, Folder 804, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1929 (Box 159, Folder 805, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1930 (Box 159, Folder 806, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1931 (Box 159, Folder 807, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: superintendent's office, 1932-1934 (Box 159, Folder 808, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Surgeon-in-Chief Fund, 1921-1933 (Box 159, Folder 809, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1915-1921 (Box 159, Folder 810, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1922-1924 (Box 159, Folder 811, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1925-1926 (Box 159, Folder 812, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1927-1929 (Box 159, Folder 813, Reel 97)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1930 (Box 159, Folder 814, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: surgeon-in-chief pro tempore, 1931-1932 (Box 159, Folder 815, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Surgical Dressing Committee, 1916 (Box 160, Folder 816, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Surgical Laboratory, 1923-1924 (Box 160, Folder 817, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital: Surgical Laboratory, 1925-1932 (Box 160, Folder 818, Reel 98)
      See also: Folder 447
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: A-Ba, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 819, Reel 98)
      See also: Folder 754; Series I, Folders 1215-1216
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: Be-Dec, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 820, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: Dee-F, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 821, Reel 98)
      See also: Folders 754-755; Series I, Folders 1215-1216
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: G-K, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 822, Reel 98)
      See also: Folders 755-756; Series I, Folders 1215-1216
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: L-M, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 823, Reel 98)
      See also: Folder 756; Series I, Folders 1215-1216
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: O, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 824, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: P-R, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 825, Reel 98)
      See also: Folder 757; Series I, Folders 1215-1216
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: Sch, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 826, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: St-Van, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 827, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants: Vas-Z, 1920-1932 (Box 160, Folder 828, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): A-B, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 829, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): C-F, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 830, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): G-H, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 831, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): J-L, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 832, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): M-O, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 833, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): P-R, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 834, Reel 98)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): S-T, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 835, Reel 99)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Voluntary assistants (abortive): V-W, 1919-1933 (Box 161, Folder 836, Reel 99)
    - The Pioneer Medical Schools of Central New York, 1934 (Box 161, Folder 837, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary body, 1909-1930 March (Box 161, Folder 838, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary body, 1930 April-1937, undated (Box 161, Folder 839, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary body, undated (Box 161, Folder 840, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary Body and Hypothalamus: correspondence and reactions, 1932-1935, undated (Box 161, Folder 841, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary Body and Hypothalamus: Thomas, Charles C., 1932 April-June (Box 161, Folder 842, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary Body and Hypothalamus: Thomas, Charles C., 1932 July (Box 161, Folder 843, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary Body and Hypothalamus: Thomas, Charles C., 1932 August-October (Box 162, Folder 844, Reel 99)
    - Pituitary Body and Hypothalamus: Thomas, Charles C., 1932 November-1938 (Box 162, Folder 845, Reel 99)
    - Poliomyelitis, 1916-1917 (Box 162, Folder 846, Reel 99)
    - Quotations notebook, undated (Box 162, Folder 847, Reel 99)
    - Reprints lists, 1923-1936 (Box 162, Folder 848, Reel 99)
    - Reprints lists, undated (Box 162, Folder 849, Reel 99)
    - Reprints lists, undated (Box 162, Folder 850, Reel 99)
    - Requests for contributions to journals, 1928-1939 (Box 162, Folder 851, Reel 100)
    - Requests for work at Yale clinic, 1936-1939 (Box 162, Folder 852, Reel 100)
    - Science firsts: A-D, 1936-1939 (Box 162, Folder 853, Reel 100)
    - Science firsts: E-L, 1936-1939 (Box 162, Folder 854, Reel 100)
    - Science firsts: M-W, 1936-1939 (Box 162, Folder 855, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration Correspondence: A-E, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 856, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration Correspondence: F-K, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 857, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration Correspondence: L-P, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 858, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration Correspondence: R-Z, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 859, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration: memorabilia and notes, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 860, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration: photographs, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 861, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration: replies, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 862, Reel 100)
    - Seventieth birthday celebration: telegrams, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 863, Reel 100)
    - Sherrington visit to U. S., 1927 (Box 163, Folder 864, Reel 100)
    - Simmons testimonial dinner, 1923-1924 (Box 163, Folder 865, Reel 100)
    - Singer visit to Boston, 1930 (Box 163, Folder 866, Reel 100)
    - Spanish democracy, 1937-1939 (Box 163, Folder 867, Reel 100)
    - Splenectomy, 1899-1900, 1928, 1934-1935 (Box 163, Folder 868, Reel 100)
    - Steamship and tourist agencies, 1922-1938 (Box 163, Folder 869, Reel 100)
    - Stiles-Connor dinner, 1923-1924 (Box 163, Folder 870, Reel 100)
    - Supplies, office, 1933-1935 (Box 163, Folder 871, Reel 100)
    - Supplies, office, 1936-1937 (Box 163, Folder 872, Reel 100)
    - Supplies, office, 1938-1939 (Box 163, Folder 873, Reel 101)
    - Surgeon General's library, 1933-1935 (Box 163, Folder 874, Reel 101)
    - Surgeon General's library, 1936-1937 (Box 164, Folder 875, Reel 101)
    - Surgeon General's library, 1938-1939 (Box 164, Folder 876, Reel 101)
    - Surgery of the Head, 1904-1924, undated (Box 164, Folder 877, Reel 101)
    - Sweden, trip to, 1929 (Box 164, Folder 878, Reel 101)
    - Sweden, trip to, 1929 (Box 164, Folder 879, Reel 101)
    - Swedish tercentenary, 1937-1939 (Box 164, Folder 880, Reel 101)
    - Symphalangism: charts and photographs, 1916, undated (Box 164, Folder 881, Reel 101)
    - Symphalangism: correspondence, 1906-1935 (Box 164, Folder 882, Reel 101)
    - Symphalangism: publications, 1901-1924 (Box 164, Folder 883, Reel 101)
    - Syracuse University address, 1933-1934 (Box 164, Folder 884, Reel 101)
    - Taylor, E. Wyllys, dinner, 1926 (Box 164, Folder 885, Reel 101)
    - Thioglycerol, 1935 (Box 164, Folder 886, Reel 101)
    - Thompson, Elihu, dinner, 1933 (Box 164, Folder 887, Reel 101)
    - Tuffier and De Page degrees, 1920 (Box 164, Folder 888, Reel 101)
    - Tumors of the Nervus Acusticus, 1917-1935 (Box 164, Folder 889, Reel 101)
    - University and hospital appointments
    - University of Paris, 1933, undated (Box 164, Folder 890, Reel 101)
    - University of Rochester School of Medicine, 1926 (Box 165, Folder 891, Reel 102)